- Like, he gon' keep talking
to me the whole ride too, man.
He was like, "So, uh,
how you doing back there?"
I was like, "Well, I'm going
to jail, nigga, not great."
"Well, you know you need to
own up to what you did."
Like, what did I do, man?
There was no victim, nigga.
Get the fuck
out my face.
- My cop tried to
get me to snitch on you.
- Word?
- Yeah, he was like,
"We both know
whose fault this is.
What was he thinking?"
- [laughs]
- It was, like, what--
a total trap.
- Man, you see?
You see how they do?
- Never been
arrested before, man.
- Yeah.
[chuckles]
Should've ditched
that weed, though.
- Yeah, there was
a lot going on,
so I kind of forgot
to do that.
It was just, like,
half a blunt.
Like, you've been
arrested for weed.
It's not that bad, right?
- Well,
it's not as good as
not getting arrested
for weed, huh?
Look...
That's Gina Simms, man.
That's Gina Simms from
that T-Pain video.
Oh, shorty is bad.
Damn.
Wonder what she's
doing here now.
- I don't know, man.
I don't think that's her.
- No, no, no, no, no.
That is definitely her,
man.
I know that ass anywhere.
You know what I mean?
- Nah, man.
- [sneezes loudly]
Gina!
[both laughing]
You see?
See, I told you.
- No, she was
trying not to look.
- Like a deer
in the headlights, like--
[both laughing]
- You think he's dead, man?
- I do not know what
you're talking about.
And now is definitely
not the time.
[PA system dings]
- [over PA] A. Miles. 278.
- All right, man, stay up.
[indistinct conversation]
[phones ringing]
[Yo Gotti's "Law" playing]
- * I'm a real hustler
* So don't knock it,
that's law *
* It's all about the re-up
* And the profit, that's law
- Okay, so here's the info
with your court date on it.
Be here before 9:00 a.m.
on the 23rd,
or they won't let you in,
and a warrant will be issued.
- So what? I'm free to go?
- Yes, sir.
They're still investigating
the shooting,
so you might have to
come back for that later,
but your bond
has already been paid
for the disorderly
conduct charge.
- Well, hold up,
what about my cousin?
Earnest Marks?
- He's not in the system yet,
but when he is,
then his bail can be posted.
- Well, what's the charge?
- What's the charge?
Nigga,
this ain't a movie.
You better wait till
he's in the system.
- [whispering]
I hate this place.
- Is that Paper Boi?
- Oh, man!
- Yo, what's up, man?
- Thank God, man.
- What it do?
Yo, you know y'all
made the news, right?
- Damn.
Wait, for real?
- Yeah.
Yeah, but 106.5 The Jam
be playing "Paper Boi"
all morning.
- Man, that's what's up.
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
- I need some food.
I ain't eat in there.
- Good.
The food in here
is genetically modified
to make you lie.
Where's Earn?
- Man, not in the system yet.
She said I can't
bail him out 'cause--
- Hey, hey, you that
paper man, right?
Ain't he the one?
- Paper Boi, man.
- Paper Boi, yeah, yeah!
Well, hold up.
Hold on, man.
I got to get a picture.
Here.
Man, I love this rap shit.
Boy, you know,
when they told me
a rapper was in here,
I had to come snap a pic.
Man, get on in here.
Hey, you listen to
Gucci Mane?
- Yeah.
- Man, I locked that nigga up!
[laughs]
Go ahead, go ahead.
[camera clicks]
Yeah. * One more
for the Insta-sluts *
* One more
for the Insta-- *
Back to back.
Come on, man,
back to back.
[camera clicks]
Nice!
That's awesome, man.
That's awe--
All right, man, see you around.
Appreciate it.
- I fucking hate
this place, man.
- Why?
[line trilling]
- Hey, it's Vanessa.
Leave a message.
Thanks. Bye.
[phone beeps]
- Hey, Van, um...
I know
you're probably mad at me.
I know you probably think
I'm pretty irresponsible,
but, um...
I'm working on something
that I think
could be really big for me.
[stammers]
And you...
too.
- [over PA] Henderson. 658.
- Yeah, I can explain all of it
when I get home.
Also, I was thinking
maybe you could bail me out?
You know, and I could
pay you back, you know, and...
- [chuckles]
- I guess rent money too.
I guess...
Yeah, so, um...
I guess I'll see you later.
Bye.
I love you.
[indistinct conversation]
- [exhales sharply]
- Hey.
[knocks]
There's no sleeping here.
Sit up.
- But...
you have to sleep.
Everybody--everybody
has always slept.
- If you want to sleep,
you got to wait
till you're processed and sent
to your cell upstairs.
- Man, can y'all please
send me upstairs?
I'm so tired.
- No.
If you want to sleep,
you should have
thought about that
before you came to jail.
- I don't believe this.
Ridiculous, man.
- Man, what'd you do
to get in here?
- Um...
- Damn, man. [stammers]
I should've just
went home, boy.
Shit, instead I'm in here,
locked up,
'cause of this fool I ain't seen
in about 11 years, man.
Boy, I was at Five Points,
'bout to catch a bus, feel me?
And this nigga I ain't seen led
me and come on talking about,
"Man, listen, hey, I ain't seen
you in about 11 years, boy.
Let's hang out.
You know, get a beer."
So I followed him
to the goddamn gas station.
We get two beers,
ain't get but two of 'em,
but they were the big ones,
though; they were the big ones.
Anyway, so he like,
"Man, come on, let's go
up to the house
and drink 'em."
So we get to the house,
he like, man,
my old lady--[murmurs]
So we gon' drink 'em
on the porch, feel me?
I'm like, "Boy, APD be
rolling through here, boy."
And he done talked me into it,
so, sure enough,
APD done roll up and seen
the goddamn two cans out there.
Locked me up
for public intoxication.
You know...
[indistinct]
Now I'm in here, man,
'cause this nigga, man,
I ain't seen
in 11 years, man.
I'm gonna be in here
till Tuesday
'cause I ain't cash my check.
- That's messed up.
- Damn, man,
I should've went home!
What?
Shit!
- Hey, man,
I said I was sorry.
I just ain't seen you in,
like, 12 years.
- Man, fuck you, Grady!
Shut up!
Not even gonna
apologize or shit.
[mumbling] Man, I hate this
motherfucking place.
Messing with garbage...
Bullshit.
- They're taking a minute, man.
- I don't know why
we ordered our food to go.
Should've just ate it here.
- Mm, man, I don't like people
watching me eat, man.
Make me feel like
I'm in a zoo.
Plus, we can't smoke weed
in here, so...
Hey, man.
Last night was crazy, right?
Shit happened so fast.
- Us humans are always
close to destruction.
Life itself is but
a series of close calls.
I mean, how would you know
you were alive
unless you knew
you could die?
- I really should be
high for this.
- Hey, yo.
Here we go.
Ten piece order.
Teriyaki wings with fries.
There you go, man.
- Thank you, man.
[sniffs] Mmm.
- Hey, yo.
I just want to say,
you the nigga, man.
- Hmm?
- You Paper Boi.
Yeah, I heard about that
shoot-out you had on Twitter.
You one of the last
real rappers, man.
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah, hey,
it's all good, fam.
You see, I'm old-school
catch, you dig?
I listen to Biggie
and Mobb Deep still.
But nowadays, you got these
singin' ass niggers
like Fetty Wap
and the gang now.
Man, that shit is weak.
- [chuckles]
- But it's good to see
a rapper that would just
blow a nigga brains out
on the street.
That's that '90s shit, B.
Hey, yo,
homeboy hooked you up.
He made you
the lemon pepper joints,
but these got
the sauce on them.
- Oh, snap.
Lemon pepper wet?
[soft triumphant music]
- Oh, my God.
- Hey, hey, yo,
my nigga.
Bring that down, man.
Yeah, see, we don't
normally do that.
But my man, Sam,
he hooked you all up.
Holla at him.
- Cool.
Cool, cool, cool.
Cool, yeah, man.
Cool.
- Hey, yo, I put a bunch of that
blue cheese in there too.
- Boom!
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, man.
- Hey, yo, keep doing
your thing, man. All right?
You one of the last
real rappers.
Keep holdin' it down,
my nigga.
- [chuckles]
- Don't let me down, man.
If you let me down...
I don't know what I'd do.
- Yo, you got
that juice, baby!
- Yeah.
[announcer speaking
foreign language]
[register beeping]
Uh, let me get a...
four-pack of them Swishers
and put the rest on pump five.
I don't need a bag.
- I know.
[Rich the Kid's
"Running Threw It" playing]
- * Bitches want to fuck me,
I got millys *
* Then I made it
know they hate it *
* Said I wouldn't do it
* I trap that pack
I got that sack *
* And now I'm running,
threw it *
* W-w-walking
with that rollie *
* Cost a fifty
* B-bitches want to
fuck me, I got millys *
* Then I made it
know they hate it *
* Said I wouldn't do it
* I trap that pack
I got that sack *
* And now I'm running,
threw it *
* W-w-w-walking
with that rollie *
- Yo, I'm gonna
go get me a Cow Tale.
- No.
- * Bitches want to fuck me
* I got millys
* Then I made it
know they hate it *
* Said I wouldn't do it
* I trap that pack
I got that sack *
* And now I'm running...
[PA system dings]
- [over PA] L. Lawson. 372.
L. Lawson. 372.
- Hey.
You gonna eat that?
- Nah, this is all you.
- [laughs]
You ain't gonna make it
in here, boy.
[man chuckling gleefully]
[indistinct conversation,
chuckling]
- What kind of dancing is that?
Lee, go sit down somewhere.
Guy never quits.
- Boy, you up in here
every week cuttin' up.
- He's in here every week?
- He was in here last time
I got locked up.
That nigga crazy.
- Hey, look, look, look, he
dipping his cup in the toilet.
- Oh, man,
he gonna drink it.
- Oh, no,
he ain't finna drink that.
all: Oh!
[laughter]
- Why is he in here
every week?
He looks like
he needs help.
- Hey, man, shut up.
- Don't tell me
that's Lee in here again.
- Yeah, it's him,
all right.
Drinking the
toilet water again.
- Oh, this guy
just keeps going.
- Ugh.
- [laughs]
- How's it going, buddy?
- [sputters]
- Oh!
[blow lands]
- Shit!
[alarm sounding]
- [screaming]
[alarm continues]
[screaming continues]
[door opens]
- Hey.
Hey, brother.
Uh, "XXL" just picked up
your story.
And...
Oh, it look like "Complex"
got you as song of the month,
brother.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
Man, that don't sound like
you think it's cool.
We should go out.
Them crazy girls that
be over at Edgewood, man,
they--they love a thug.
You gonna clean it all up.
- Nah, man, I don't know, man.
I'm not feeling it.
I don't feel like
being around people today.
I just...
getting this weird, like,
energy today.
- Well, yo, maybe we could go
shoot some pool, all right?
They cool up there.
Plus, you know,
you could talk to
that little waitress, you know,
with the hair thing going on.
- Yeah, maybe.
- Yeah, buddy.
[cell phone chimes]
- Oh. Hey, bro.
I got a Google Alert
set up on you,
and it look like "Vibe"
wrote one.
It says...
"Is Paper Boi
Atlanta's Tupac?"
[door closes]
They said no.
But, apparently, John Boyega
is the new Magic Johnson.
Huh.
[children yelling]
[toy gun beeping]
- [imitating
machine gun fire]
Just like Paper Boi, girl.
- Let me see it, DeMario.
- Back up.
Or I'll smoke you, man.
- Boy!
What is your problem?
Didn't I tell you
that we do not
play with guns
in this house?
Where you get this from?
- My friend, Alex.
- I better not catch you
playing with
no toy guns again, boy.
- He was playing like
he was Paper Boi.
- I don't care, Angel,
we don't play like that.
Come on.
- Hey.
Hey!
Hey, I just wanted to come over,
'cause I just saw that,
and I wanted to tell y'all...
you know,
that shooting people,
that isn't cool.
- Yeah, I know.
Who are you, and why are you
speaking to me and my children?
- Uh... Oh, no. I...
I didn't mean to just
get in your business.
- Yeah, but you did.
- Look, I may be to blame,
'cause...
you know,
I'm actually Paper Boi.
- Who?
- Paper Boi.
The rapper that
your child was imitating.
- You ain't Paper Boi, man!
- Yeah, I am, you little ba--
Paper Boi.
* Paper Boi, Paper Boi
* All about that paper boy
- Wha...
Wait a second.
I heard that today
in the car.
I think my girlfriend
was talking about you.
- Hey.
- Oh, go get my phone
out my purse, boy, go.
Oh, my goodness.
[laughs]
This crazy.
What you doing here?
- Well--no, I'm from
around the way, so...
Look, I ain't mean
to get in your business.
- You shot somebody.
- Quiet, girl.
Your mama be here soon,
don't start now.
Only, uh, DeMario my son.
This is just
my niece and nephew.
Say hey, y'all.
Hey.
[together] Hey.
- Hey, guys.
- Well, um, let me get a
picture with you, Mr. Rap Star.
[giggles]
I'm gonna send it
to my girl Ebony.
- Oh, all right.
- Come on, y'all.
Come get in this pic, come on.
- Okay, oh--
it's a family portrait,
okay.
Um...
- Y'all smile, now.
[camera clicks]
All right, move, let me
get a picture with mama.
So take this, DeMario.
Let me put my head
on your chest, okay?
- Oh, okay.
- Take it, DeMario,
hurry up.
[camera clicks]
- I haven't seen you
in forever.
Hey, you remember '12?
Your hair was brown.
- Oh, I remember.
Honey, I was in a completely
different space back then.
- Nah, nah, it's nice now.
I like it.
You always did like
to switch it up.
- I can move,
if you want.
- Yeah, I know.
Yeah, I was wildin'
back then.
[chuckles]
You remember Larry?
- No.
Larry?
- Yeah, yeah, Larry.
Used to come around
with Kevin.
He went to Southwest.
- Um, I think so.
I remember Kevin.
He was loud.
- Larry came with us
to the movies that time.
I know you remember
the movies, now.
We used to get freaky
in there all the time.
Remember that?
- Quiet.
- Oh, don't act, girl,
you know we used to get it in.
Hey, where you stay at now?
Hey, man, what's
your problem, man?
- No, I--no problem.
I can move, if you want--
- I ain't ask you
to move, nigga!
I'm trying to talk to my girl,
you acting all weird and shit.
- Your girl?
- Yeah, man.
Yo, this is my ex,
Lisa, man.
We used to talk back after
my moms kicked me out the house.
- My nigga, that's a man.
- Wha--no, man,
this is my ex.
- Your ex-girlfriend a man.
Why you think she
in jail with the men?
She'd be on the other side.
Nigga, you gay.
- No, man, she--
[chuckles] Nah, man.
So you think I'm gay?
- Nah.
No, I--
- This nigga gay as hell.
[laughter]
- Shut the hell up, man!
Y'all niggas is tripping!
Man, I ain't gay!
Y'all niggas fuck guys
up in here, anyway.
- No, that--that ain't gay;
that's just jail.
You was on the outside
fucking booty holes.
[laughter]
- Sexuality is a spectrum.
You can really do
whatever you want.
- Man, that boy
gay as hell.
- I'm gonna stab your old ass
when we get upstairs
to them cells, man.
Nigga, sit down!
- Johnny, calm down--
- Everyone can shut
the fuck up, now!
I know what you all
think she is...
But I ain't on
that faggot shit, man.
Stop being weird, nigga!
- I'm not--I'm trying--
No, man, I'm just sitting here.
- All y'all shut up.
This ain't fun time.
- Oh, what it do, man?
Where'd you go?
I didn't even notice
you left.
- I just went out
for a second.
I did get this girl's
number, though.
[both laughing]
- I know you did.
'Cause you,
you got that juice.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
[knock at door]
- Paper Boi live here?
- Uh, yeah?
- Okay.
- You too hot.
- All right,
let's go, everybody.
We're heading upstairs.
- Man, thank you.
[PA system dings]
- E. Marks.
- I'm him.
[thunder rumbles]
[tapping on window]
Thanks for bailing me out.
[Lottie babbling]
- Hey, Mama.
- * Out came the sun
* And dried all the rain
- She won't remember this.
It'll be like...
"Hey, remember that time
"we had to pick up Daddy
from jail?
"Me neither,
'cause I'm a baby
"and I don't
remember anything.
And my brain
isn't developed yet."
- You can shut up now.
- I know.
[engine turns over]
[Bill Withers'
"Grandma's Hands" playing]
- * Mm-hmm
* Mm-hmm
* Grandma's hands
* Clapped in church on
Sunday morning *
* Grandma's hands
* Played the tambourine
so well *
* Grandma's hands
* Used to issue out a warning
* She'd say
* Billy,
don't you run so fast *
* Might fall on
a piece of glass *
* Might be snakes there
in that grass *
* Grandma's hands
*
* Sooth the local
unwed mother *
* Grandma's hands
* Used to ache sometimes
and swell *
* Mm-hmm-mm